Hello there.
My name is audio jack on the vice president of
education at UT Sciences Toastmasters.
We are a community of students on campus,
dedicated to improving our public speaking.
And professional skills.
We do this at meetings,
which we hold every Friday from 6 to 7.
We continue to hold meetings,
over summer,
be a zoom and we encourage you to join us.
Links will be in the description to give you an
idea of what a meeting is like and how we
help our members improve their public speaking.
We're going to take the next 10 minutes to take
a one-hour meeting and shrink it down into those 10
minutes.
I lack of the Toastmaster of the evening which means
I will conduct the meeting and transition between our speakers.
We're going to have to speaking session.
The first speaking section is called prepared speeches,
Sarah,
and Spencer,
have both prepared a speech for us and we'll hear
what they have to say.
And our second part of the meeting is called table.
Topics.
Ming will volunteer himself to come up on stage and
I will give him a question that he's never considered
before he left to speak on the spot or around
one to two minutes.
Let's get started.
First is Sora delivering a speech on what UT science
is Toastmasters mean to her.
Thank you,
sir for that very inspiring speech.
It's nice to know that even those who look like
they are going to public speaking.
Sometimes have struggles and I think that's something that every
member at your designs is Jump Masters.
Can I test you?
Next up,
we have Spencer Spencer is our vice president of membership
and he's going to be talking to you about how
Toastmasters helped him transition to UT answer,
take it away.
Austin Spencer again,
what a great story about how hard it is to
transition to college.
Thank you Spencer for telling us that story.
It's nice to know that everyone deals with transition times
and different way.
Donkey Spencer for such a well,
thought-out speech.
It's nice to know that everyone knows now.
What do we do?
What a nice Beach Spencer.
Thank you.
Answer is one of our most dedicated members.
And again,
just thank you Spencer for sharing your experience.
Now,
I'm going to move on to the second part of
our meeting,
which is the table topics main has volunteered to be
our first tabletopics contestant.
I will ask him a question and then he will
have to respond on the spot.
Here is your question,
meaning.
You going on a road trip when suddenly your GPS
stops working.
Where were you going and what do you do next?
Very nice man.
Just like Dorothy says,
just keep swimming.
Ming says,
just keep driving.
Would that that is the end of our mini meeting.
If you were buying from more speeches and more interaction,
please check out our meeting.
You can find us on Facebook.
UT science is Toastmasters.
That's utstein.
You can also check out our mailing list at the
bottom of this YouTube video.
We will have a link to a Google form where
you can sign up to be part of our mailing
list.
If you are at all interested in seeing what a
full meeting is,
like,
I encourage you to come for this Friday until then.