Pretty clouds fluffy.
What what?
I didn't say anything.
You know a friend of mine actually designed these were
balloons.
No kidding a balloon,
but for war there's one thing my dad's good at
its War.
Yeah,
it seems to run in the family.
Hey,
hold on.
Not everyone in my family like that.
I know.
I know you changed.
I meant my uncle.
He was more of a father than me.
And I really let him down.
I think your uncle would be proud of you.
Leaving your home to come help us.
That's hard.
Wasn't that hard?
Really?
You didn't leave behind any one you cared about?
Well,
I did have a girlfriend.
May that gloomy girl,
you size a lot.
Yeah.
Everyone in the Fire Nation thinks I'm a traitor.
I couldn't drag her into it.
My First Girlfriend turned into the Moon.
That's rough,
buddy.